Register of the John Vaizey Papers, 1926-1985
Hoover Institution Archives
- PHOTOGRAPHS.
  - 5 group photographs, including Hugh Dalton, Clement Attlee, Ernest Bevin, Winston Churchill, Jawaharlal Nehru, other Cabinet ministers (?), circa 1945-1947; 4 prints of Hugh Dalton and colleagues in ceremonial robes; 4 prints of Hugh Dalton at a political march in Durham, 1956; 2 prints of Hugh Dalton in a presentation ceremony, 1947 (Envelope C)
  - 2 portrait prints of Hugh Dalton (Envelope mD)